Guide to the International Monitor Institute Records, 1986-2006 and undated RL.00604
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Organizational Records Series, 1986-2006, 43 boxes
  - Balkan Archives Subseries, 1986-2006 and undated
    - International Criminal Tribunal of the Former Yugoslavia (ICTY), 1993-1997
      - International Arrest Warrants and Orders for Surrender, 1996 Jul. (Box OR8)
      - Karadzic, Radovan, miscellaneous court document, 1996 June (Box OR8)
      - List of indictees and camps, 1995-1996 (Box OR8)
      - Edward Medvene and Thomas Hanley, Notice of Appearance and Request for Permission on behalf of Dr. Radovan Karadzic, 1996 Jul. 5 (Box OR8)
      - Motions, 1996 Apr.-Aug. (Box OR8)
      - Order for Measures of Protection for Witness X, 1996 Oct. 18 (Box OR8)
      - Phone list, 1995 Oct. 1 (Box OR8)
      - Press releases, 1996-1997 (Box OR9)
      - Reports, statements and sources on Yugoslavia, including documentary footage and other sources, 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box OR9)
      - Request for accreditation of media representatives and itinerary, 1994 (Box OR9)
      - Rule 61 Hearing and Proceedings, 1995-1996 (Box OR9)
      - Rules of Procedure and Evidence, 1996 Jul. (Box OR9)
      - Tadic trial, opening statements by Grant Niemann (prosecution) and Michael Wladimiroff (defence), 1996 May 7 (Box OR9)
      - Transcripts, 1996-2001
        - Generals Galic and Krstic, and Dusko Sikirica, 2000 Jul. (Box OR9)
        - Blaskic, General Tihomir, 1997-2001, 1 of 2 (Box OR9)
        - Blaskic, General Tihomir, 1997-2001, 2 of 2 (Box OR10)
        - Karanovic, Rajko regarding prior knowledge of Tadic, 1996 Sep. 18-20 (Box OR10)
        - Kordic, Dario, 2000 Jul., 3 folders (Box OR10)
        - Kunarac, Dragoljub, Book 1, 2000 Jul., 4 of 5 (Box OR10)
        - Kunarac, Dragoljub, Book 1, 2000 Jul., 5 of 5 folders (Box OR11)
        - Kunarac, Dragoljub, Book 2, 2000 Jul., 3 folders (Box OR11)
        - Kvocka, Miroslav, 2000 Jul., 2 of 4 folders (Box OR11)
        - Kvocka, Miroslav, 2000 Jul., 3-4 of 4 folders (Box OR11)
        - Milosevic trial records, Book 1, 2002 Feb., 1 of 2 (Box OR11)
        - Milosevic trial records, Book 1, 2002 Feb., 2 of 2 folders (Box OR12)
        - Milosevic trial records, Book 2, 2002 Feb., 2 folders (Box OR12)
        - Milosevic trial records, Book 3, 2002 Feb. 3, 3 folders (Box OR12)
        - Milosevic trial records, Book 4, 2002 Feb.-Mar., 1 of 3 (Box OR12)
        - Milosevic trial records, Book 4, 2002 Feb.-Mar., 2-3 of 3 folders (Box OR13)
        - Tadic, Dusko defense, 1996, 2 folders (Box OR13)
        - Tadic, Dukso opening statement of the defense in the case of, undated (Box OR13)
      - Video collection, 1995-1996 (Box OR13)
      - Video movement log, 1996 (Box OR13)
    - International Commission of Missing Persons press release, "Delegation of Colombian scientists visits ICMP," 2009 Mar. (Box OR13)
    - International Crisis Group, "Aid and Accountability: Dayton Implementation," (Sarajevo), 1996 Nov. 24 (Box OR13)
    - International Human Rights Law Institute: Yugoslavia video database, 1993 (Box OR13)
    - Internationaal Instituut voor Sociale Geschiedenis, 1994 (Box OR13)
    - International Medical Corps, "War Trauma Among Refugee Children in Zenica, BiH," 1994 Apr. (Box OR13)
    - IMI brochure photos, Bosnia, 1995-1996 (Box OR13)
    - Italiafiction TV Festival, 1994 (Box OR13)
    - Journal Graphics, Inc., topic alert service report, 1994, Aug. 25 (Box OR13)
    - Kalaba, Kosovo, 1994 and undated (Box OR13)
    - Khayyam Productions, 1994 and undated (Box OR13)
    - Kosovo conflict, miscellaneous, 1999 (Box OR14)
    - Kosovo/Milosevic documentary, 1998 (Box OR14)
    - "Kosovo: Statement by the President of the ICTY, Gabrielle Kirk McDonald," 1999 Mar. 31 (Box OR14)
    - Last Train Out: A True Story of Love and War in Bosnia, by William Turck, 1995 (Box OR14)
    - L.A. Times, 1994-1995 (Box OR14)
    - Law schools and universities volunteers, 1993-1995 (Box OR14)
    - Lawyer to Lawyer Network, Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, "Nikola Barovic - Serbia, 1997 Jul. (Box OR14)
    - Lelieveld, Joeri tape log, 2004-2005 (Box OR14)
    - List of indictees, as of 1996 Jan. 1 (Box OR14)
    - List of names regarding Kosovo, 1999 Mar. 31 (Box OR14)
    - List of Radio Television Belgrade/TV Serbia footage in the possession of someone in Belgrade represented by a Mr. Lalic, undated (Box OR14)
    - A Living Wall,Former Yugoslavia: Zagreb, Slavonski Brod, and Sarajevo, by Pippa Scot and Mary Ann Schawlbe, 1993, Oct. 3-18 (Box OR14)
    - London Peace Implementation Conference, 1996: Bosnia and Herzecovina, 1997: Making Peace Work (Box OR14)
    - "The Making of a War Crimes Tribunal," documentary project, 1994 and undated (Box OR14)
    - "Manipulations on Television Belgrade," by Milica Pesic, 1994 (Box OR14)
    - Miscellaneous file, including media, 1993-1996 and undated (Box OR14)
    - Miscellaneous organizations, 1993-1994 (Box OR15)
    - Miscellaneous proposal backup, 1995 (Box OR15)
    - National Public Radio (NPR), acquisition of material, 1995 Aug. 17 (Box OR15)
    - Nederlandse Omroepprogramma Stichting (NOS) listing of reports on the civil war in former Yugoslavia, 1992, 1994 (Box OR15)
    - The New Combat: A Journal of Reason and Resistance, Death in Sarajevo, director Haris Prolic, 1995, Jan. (Box OR15)
    - New York Times articles on Balkans, 1994-1997 (Box OR15)
    - NGO Information Centre communique, 1996 Dec. 5-6 (Box OR15)
    - Northstar Productions - Sarajevo shot list, 1993 (Box OR15)
    - Notebook of Pippa Scott, undated (Box OR15)
    - "On Trial: The United Nations, War Crimes, and the Former Yugoslavia," by Ian Guest, 1995 Sep. (Box OR15)
    - Open letter from Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe to President Cliton regarding Sarajevo, 1993 Jul. 23 (Box OR15)
    - Open Society archives, 1999 (Box OR15)
    - Open Society Institute Croatia tapes, 1998-1999 (Box OR15)
    - Open Society Institute tapes copy, 1990-1991 (Box OR15)
    - Outreach ideas to pursue, 1993-1994 (Box OR15)
    - People, 1990-2006
      - Bassiouni, Cherif Professor, 1990-2006, 1 of 3 (Box OR15)
      - Bassiouni, Cheri Professor, 1990-2006, 2-3 of3 folders (Box OR16)
      - Berry Sheila (ICTY), correspondence regarding funding negotiations for Balkan Archive, 1995-1996 (Box OR16)
      - Blewitt, Graham (ICTY), 1994-1999 (Box OR16)
      - Blitz, Brad, Students Against Genocide (SAGE), 1993-1995 (Box OR16)
      - Bryant, Lee, 1995 (Box OR16)
      - Burns, Tracy, De Paul University, College of Law, regarding tapes, 1994 (Box OR16)
      - Cataldi, Anna, 1997 (Box OR16)
      - Ciesniewsky, Tony, President, The Balkan Archive, 1996 (Box OR16)
      - Cohen, Beth, Bosnian Student Project, 1995 (Box OR16)
      - Dosti, Victor - 1. "Prison Nation" documentary, 2. New York Times article regarding Albanian prison camp, 3. speeches, 1999 (Box OR16)
      - Du Toit, J.J. (ICTY), 1995 (Box OR16)
      - Erdemovic, Drazen, 1997-1999 (Box OR16)
      - Forester, Patricia, Citizens Commission for Human Rights, 1995 (Box OR16)
      - Gardner, Ellen, appointment as video analyst for United Nations, 1995-1998 (Box OR16)
      - Gajic, Goran, 1993 (Box OR16)
      - Grubesa, Tomislav, Mission of Bosnia-Herzogovina, 1995 (Box OR16)
      - Gutman, Roy, Newsday, 1993-1996 (Box OR16)
      - Harrison, Lisa, BBC (Box OR17)
      - Loza, Tihomar, 1995 (Box OR17)
      - Memija, Mufid, Advisor to President of Republic of Bosnia-Hercegovina and General Manager of Radio-TV of Bosnia-Herzogovina, 1993-1995 (Box OR17)
      - Paepen, Jozef, Head of Liaison Office, Zagreb, 1998 (Box OR17)
      - Janney, Richard, Project Director, De Paul University, 1993 (Box OR17)
      - Riedlmayer, Andras, The Aga Khan Program, 1994-1997 (Box OR17)
      - Rogers, Hillary, 1994-1996 (Box OR17)
      - Scheffer, David, Ambassador at Large for War Crimes Issues, 1997-1998 (Box OR17)
      - Sharfi, Cindy, 1999 Jan. (Box OR17)
      - Stamkoski, George, M.D., Media East West, including "The UN's Balkan War," 1995-1996 (Box OR17)
      - Steubner, Bill, 1994 (Box OR17)
      - Sullivan, Stacey, 1999 (Box OR17)
      - Tanovic-Miller, Naza, Bosna Film, 1994-1995 (Box OR17)
      - Van Cleef, Alfred, "The Lost World of the Berberovic Family," undated (Box OR17)
      - Warrick, Tom, regarding Bosnia War Crimes Project, 1993-1996, 2 folders (Box OR17)
    - Political parties, former Yugoslavia, 1996 June 20 (Box OR17)
    - "A Prima Facie Case for the Indictment of Slobodan Milosevic," by Paul Williams and Norman Cigar, 1996 (Box OR17)
    - Pro-Croat propaganda, 1991-1993 (Box OR17)
    - Pro-Serb propaganda, 1993 and undated (Box OR17)
    - Rape as war crime, 1993 and undated (Box OR17)
    - "Rape, War, and the Military," Madeline Morris, 1995 Aug. 16 (Box OR18)
    - Refugees, Bosnia, 1993-1994 (Box OR18)
    - Report on violations at Luka and Brcko camps, undated (Box OR18)
    - Republika Srbija, 1995 Aug. 16 (Box OR18)
    - Research material, 6/Parter, 1997-1999 (Box OR18)
    - Reuters, 1993-1995 (Box OR18)
    - The Riehle Foundation, Croatia, 1991 Nov. 22 (Box OR18)
    - Rights and Wrongs, Human Rights Television - "Yellow Wasps," Part 1, 1995 May 31 (Box OR18)
    - Rem Koolhaas and OMA, undated (Box OR18)
    - The Role of Mass Media in the Serbia-Crotian Conflict, ed. Marjan Malesic, 1992 (Box OR18)
    - Ron Haviv documentary, 1999-2000 (Box OR18)
    - Roy Gutman (Newsday) footage search, 1994-1995 (Box OR18)
    - Sarajevo Group of Authors (SAGA), 1993-1994 and undated (Box OR18)
    - Students Against Genocide (SAGE), "The Serbian Unity Congress and the Serbian Lobby: A Study of Contemporary Revisionism and Denial," 1994 Oct. 18 (Box OR18)
    - Serbian Academy of Arts and Sciences, memorandum, 1986 (Box OR18)
    - "The Serbian Genocide, 1941-1945" (booklet), undated (Box OR19)
    - Serbnet, correspondence regarding documentary tapes, 1994 Mar.-Apr. (Box OR19)
    - "Sexual Violence: An Invisible Weapon of War in the Former Yugoslavia," by Cherif Bassiouni and Marcia McCormick, 1996 (Box OR19)
    - Shot lists - civil war in Yugoslavia, Serajevo, undated (Box OR19)
    - S. Kadic v. Radovan Kardzic, Plaintiffs' Memorandum in Opposition to Defendant's Motion to Dismiss Prior to Answer, No. 93-Civ-1163, 1993 (Box OR19)
    - Sky News broadcast logs, 1990-1995
      - Camera rushes, Bosnia, 1991-1995 (Box OR19)
      - Library masters, Bosnia, 1992 (Box OR19)
      - External sources, Bosnia, 1992-1995 (Box OR19)
      - Library masters, Bosnia, 1993 (Box OR19)
      - Unidentified sources, Bosnia, 1994 (Box OR19)
      - Library masters, Bosnia, 1995 (Box OR19)
      - All sources, Croatia, 1991-1994 (Box OR19)
      - All sources, General Mladic, 1992-1995 (Box OR19)
      - All sources, Macedonia, 1991-1994 (Box OR19)
      - All sources, Serbia, 1991-1995 (Box OR19)
      - All sources, Slovenia, 1990-1994 (Box OR19)
      - Library masters, Yugoslavia, 1990-1991 (Box OR20)
      - Camera rushes and external sources, Yugoslavia, 1990-1995 (Box OR20)
      - Library masters, Yugoslavia, 1991 (Box OR20)
    - Slide presentations regarding footage on Yugoslavia, undated (Box OR20)
    - Source lists, 1993-1994 and undated (Box OR20)
    - Spiegal interview with Slobodan Milosevic: "The Key to Peace," 1996 June 10 (Box OR20)
    - Stupni Do slaughter, concentration camps, etc., 1992-1993 (Box OR20)
    - Sveriges Television (SVT) listing - material print-outs, 1993 (Box OR20)
    - Tape for rape investigation, 1994 (Box OR20)
    - Tapes from Belgrade search, 1995-1996 (Box OR20)
    - Tape shots of Bosnia-Hercegovina, 1993 and undated (Box OR20)
    - Tapes, miscellaneous information, 1993-1995 and undated (Box OR20)
    - Translators, 1994-1995 (Box OR20)
    - Tribunal and bulletin publications and related documents, 1996-1997 (Box OR20)
    - Tribunal articles regarding Yugoslavia/Bosnia, 1995-1997 (Box OR20)
    - Tribunal documentary, 1995 (Box OR20)
    - Tribunal tapes, 1996 (Box OR20)
    - Tribunal video project, undated (Box OR20)
    - TV Bih video-archiva listing, undated (Box OR20)
    - TV Library Services batch report, 1993 Apr. 1-Dec. 31 (Box OR21)
    - United Nations Commission of Experts (Box OR21)
    - United Nations Forces Bosnia, 1993 (Box OR21)
    - United Nations International Tribunal for the Prosecution of Persons Responisble for Serious Violations of International Humanitarian Law Committed in the Territory of Former Yugoslavia Since 1991, In the Trial Chamber, 1996 June (Box OR21)
    - United Nations International Tribunal for the Prosecution of Persons Responisble for Serious Violations of International Humanitarian Law Committed in the Territory of Former Yugoslavia Since 1991, Rules of Procedure of Evidence, 1996 Apr. (Box OR21)
    - United Nations Special Commission (UNSCOM) footage, 1998 (Box OR21)
    - United Nation Security Council, letter from Secretary General to Presidence of Security Council, 1994 May 24 (Box OR21)
    - War crimes - concentration camps, 1999 and undated (Box OR21)
    - War crimes montage, undated (Box OR21)
    - War crimes tape descriptions, 1999 (Box OR21)
    - War Crimes Tribunal report, 1994 (Box OR21)
    - War Crimes Tribunal articles, 1993 and undated (Box OR21)
    - War Report: Bulletin of the Institute of War and Peace Reporting, 1997 Mar. (Box OR21)
    - Witness and Balkan Archives, 1996-1999 (Box OR21)
    - Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children, 1992-1993 (Box OR21)
    - "Working for Peace in the Balkans: A Guide to U.S. Organizations," 1996 (Box OR21)
    - Yugoslavia, Origins of War, proposed by Marie Claude Vogric, Producer, Krzysztof Talczewski, 1994 (Box OR21)
    - Zagreb Commission of Experts trip, 1994 Feb.-Mar. (Box OR21)
  - Asia Pacific Archives Subseries, 1989-2001 and undated
    This subseries contains material on human rights abuses in Burma (Myanmar), Cambodia, China, East Timor/Indonesia, Japan, Laos, Thailand and Vietnam. The bulk of material is from the Burma and Cambodia archives. Records include correspondence regarding funding and other support for the archives, conference materials and conference travel itineraries, numerous reports from Human Rights Watch and Amnesty International on various human rights conflicts in the Asia Pacific region as well as a number of reports and other materials from the Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children. Other records and correspondence include IMI's contact with other human rights organizations operating out of the Asia Pacific. Further audiovisual material on Burma can be found in the International Monitor Institute Burma Archive records, also at the Rubenstein Library.
    - Burma Archive (Box 0R22)
      - Amnesty International - Myanmar forced labor, 1998 (Box 0R22)
      - Burma Archive correspondence, 1997 (Box 0R22)
      - Burma Archive funding - correspondence and proposals, 1997 Mar. (Box 0R22)
      - Burma Archive general, 1997 (Box 0R22)
      - Burma conference itinerary, 1998 Oct. 2-4 (Box 0R22)
      - Burma conference, 1998 Oct. (Box 0R22)
      - Burma political timeline, undated (Box 0R22)
      - Burma publications, including interview transcripts, 1996 (Box 0R22)
      - "False Peace: Increasing SPDC Military Repression in Toungoo District of Northern Karen State," 1999 Mar. (Box 0R22)
      - Hallacy, Jeanne, 1998-1999 (Box 0R22)
      - "Human Rights Violations Committed by Units/Personnel of Burma's SLORC Armed Forces, 1994-1995," 1996 June (Box 0R22)
      - Human Rights Watch - "Bangladesh/Burma: Rohingy Refugees in Bangladesh: The Search for a Lasting Solution," report, 1997 Aug. (Box 0R22)
      - Human Rights Watch Asia - "Burma Children's Rights and the Rule of Law," report, 1997 Jan. (Box 0R22)
      - Human Rights Watch Asia - "Burma/Thailand: No Safety in Burma, No Sanctuary in Thailand," report 1997 Jul. (Box 0R22)
      - Images Asia - Lyndal, Barry, 1996-1998 (Box 0R22)
      - Karen Human Rights Group - photo description list: set 99-A, 1999 Mar. (Box 0R22)
      - Karen refugees in Thailand, Bangkok Post, 1997 Mar. (Box 0R22)
      - Open Society Institute, 1997 (Box 0R22)
      - "SPDC Orders to Villages, Set 99-B: Thaton and Pa'an Districts, Karen State," 1999 Apr. (Box 0R22)
      - State Department, Burma, various documents, 1997-1998 and undated (Box 0R22)
    - Cambodia Archive
      - Asia Watch Cambodia, 1993 May and Sep. (Box 0R22)
      - Asia Watch - human rights in Cambodia, 1990-1993 (Box 0R22)
      - "Beyond Traditional Peacekeeping: The Case of Cambodia," by James Schear, Center for Naval War Studies, 1994 Feb. 24 (Box 0R22)
      - Cambodia Archive correspondence, 1997 (Box 0R22)
      - Cambodia articles, 1997 (Box 0R22)
      - "Cambodia Can't Wait: Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children," report, 1993 Feb. 8-20 (Box 0R22)
      - Cambodia Genocide Project, Yale University, 1995-1997 (Box 0R22)
      - The Cambodian National Archives, 1998 (Box OR23)
      - Cambodia trip and general information, 1997 (Box OR23)
      - Cambodia/Vietnam trip, 1997 (Box OR23)
      - Children of the Dust by Mikel Flamm, 1997-1998 (Box OR23)
      - Communicating for Change: Report on Women and Media Workshop, 1996 Jan. 16-19 (Box OR23)
      - Etcheson, Craig, 1997-1999 (Box OR23)
      - Flamm, Mikel, including photos of Khmer Rouge exodus (on disc) and additional material, 1998 (Box OR23)
      - Human Rights Watch Asia - "Cambodia: Aftermath of the Coup, report," 1997 Aug. (Box OR23)
      - Khmer Rouge, 1998 (Box OR23)
      - "The Making of the Paris Agreement on Cambodia, 1990-1991," by Ben Kiernan, presented at Indochina Project Conference, 1991 Dec. (Box OR23)
      - Mayotte, Judith - letter about Cambodian experience, 1990 Nov. 4 (Box OR23)
      - News articles, 1989-1997 (Box OR23)
      - "Political Control, Human Rights, and the UN Mission in Cambodia," Asia Watch 1992 Sep. (Box OR23)
      - "Review of the Cambodia Repatriation Operation," by Jeff Crsip and Andrew Mayne, 1993 Sep. (Box OR23)
      - United Nations General Assembly and Security Council documents, 1992-1993 (Box OR23)
      - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees: Repatriation Operation, Cambodia, 1992 Aug. 3 (Box OR23)
      - United Nations Peacekeeping Mission articles, 1994 and undated (Box OR23)
      - United Nations Transitional Authority, Cambodia, 1991-1992 (Box OR23)
      - "Women and Children in Crisis: Inside Burma and Along the Thai Border," Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children, report, undated (Box OR23)
      - Women's Media Centre list of video and audio productions, 1997 Jan. (Box OR23)
      - Yale Center for International and Area Studies, "Documenting the Cambodian Genocide on Multimedia, 1998 Oct. (Box OR23)
      - Zucker, Eve Monique regarding Cambodia tapes, 1998 Oct. (Box OR23)
    - China
      - Asia Watch - prison labor and conditions in China, reports, 1991 and 1997 (Box OR23)
      - China, general, 2000 and undated, 1 of 2 (Box OR23)
      - China, general, 2000 and undated, 2 of 2 folders (Box OR24)
      - Hong Kong, 1997 (Box OR24)
      - Human Rights Watch Asia - "China: Chinese Diplomacy, Western Hypocrisy and the U.N. Human Rights Commission," report, 1997 Mar. (Box OR24)
      - Human Rights Watch Asia - "China: State of Control of Religion," report, 1997 Oct. (Box OR24)
      - Human Rights Watch Asia - "China: Whose Security? 'State Security' in China's New Criminal Code," report, 1997 Apr. (Box OR24)
      - Human Rights Watch Asia - "Hong Kong: Abuses Against Vietnamese Asylum Seekers in the Final Days of the Comprehensive Plan of Action," reports, 1997 Mar. (Box OR24)
    - Indonesia
      - East Timor, Journeyman transcripts, 1999 (Box OR24)
      - General organizational and press records, 2000-2001 (Box OR24)
      - Human Rights Watch - "Indonesia: Communal Violance in West Kalimantan," report, 1997 Dec. (Box OR24)
      - Human Rights Watch Asia - "Indonesia/East Timor: Deteriorating Human Rights in East Timor," reports, 1995 Feb. and 1997 Sep. (Box OR24)
      - "Indonesia: Release Prisoners of Conscience Now!" undated (Box OR24)
    - Japan
      - Japanese footage search, 1993-1994 (Box OR24)
      - Japanese Unit 731 and Mihokoho Tokoro regarding unit, 1999 and undated (Box OR24)
    - Lao People's Democratic Republic
      - "Country Report on Women in the Lao PDR," the 4th World Conference on Women, 1995 (Box OR24)
      - Essential Laos, undated (Box OR24)
      - Information Package for the Office of the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees n the Lao PDR, 1998 June 22 (Box OR24)
      - Laos articles, 1997-1998 (Box OR24)
      - Laos fact sheets - narcotics, American Embassy, prisoners of war and missing in action task force, and humanitarian demining assistance, undated (Box OR24)
      - Laos Women's Union, "The Art of Silk," undated (Box OR24)
      - Mahosoth hospital data sheet, Vientiane, 1996 (Box OR24)
      - Map of Vientiane, Lao PDR, 1993 (Box OR24)
      - "Mission Performance Plan Goals," Margaret K. McMillion, U.S. Embassy Vietiane, undated (Box OR24)
      - Overview, undated (Box OR24)
      - Repatriation information, United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees branch office, Vientiane, 1997 Mar.-Jul. (Box OR24)
      - Xaythanee District Group Guaranteed Lending and Savings Project, undated (Box OR24)
    - Thailand
      - Bankok articles, undated (Box OR24)
      - Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children, mission to Thailand, 1989 June 19-24 (Box OR24)
    - Tibet
      - Tibet House, "Peacemaking: The Power of Nonviolence," conference with Nobel Peace Laureates, 1997 June 9-11 (Box OR24)
      - "Violence and Discrimination Against Tibetan Women," repot by International Committee of Lawyers for Tibet, Women's Commission for Refugee Women and Children, and Tibetan Centre for Human Rights and Democracy, 1998 Dec. (Box OR24)
    - Vietnam
      - Cinema, 1996 (Box OR24)
      - General, undated (Box OR24)
      - Human Rights Watch Asia - "Vietnam: Human Rights in a Season of Transition: Law and Dissent in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam, 1995 Aug. (Box OR24)
      - Human Rights Watch - "Vietnam: Rural Unrest in Vietnam, report, 1997 Dec. (Box OR24)
      - News articles, 1998 (Box OR25)
      - Vietnamese refugee women and children, 1989-1990 (Box OR25)
      - Vietnam organizations - assistance with film on history, culture, lifestyle, etc., 1997 (Box OR25)
      - Vietnam relief organization pamphlets, undated (Box OR25)
      - "Vietnam Report on Human Rights Practices for 1996," United States Department of State, 1997 Jan. 30 (Box OR25)
    - Southeast Asia Interregional and Other
      - Dispatch - Indochina, 1994 May-Nov. (Box OR25)
      - Film-tracking - BBC regarding Indochina-Vietnam, 1993-1995 (Box OR25)
      - Indochina Interchange, 1997 Dec. (Box OR25)
      - Southeast Asia Archive proposals, 1997 (Box OR25)
      - Southeast Asia - phone lists, undated (Box OR25)
      - Southeast Asia Resource Action Center (SEARAC) visit, undated (Box OR25)
      - Southeast Asia trip, 1998 (Box OR25)
      - United States Air Force motion pictures film depository footage catalogue - Southeast Asia, 1944-1967 (Box OR25)
      - United States and Pacific article, New York Times, 2001 Nov. 15 (Box OR25)
  - Middle East Archives Subseries, 1989-2001 and undated